PERSONAL INFORMATION



Manly vale, NSW. Australia



santiago.debrito12@gmail.com



(+61) 452156572



santiagodebrito12.github.io/Portfoliosantiagodebrito/



/santiagodebrito

HARD SKILLS



HTML



CSS



Javascript



React

T. Next Js



Node Js



Express



Mongo DB



Docker



GIT / Github

SOFT SKILLS

- English- TOEFL Exam Certificate
- **Proactive Personality**
- Excellent intrapersonal handling
- Teamwork

SANTIAGO DE BRITO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Nationality:: Argentino Working & Holiday Visa 462

PERSONAL SUMARY

I am a passionate developer born in Patagonia, Argentina. I am a Frontend developer with more than 2 years of experience developing digital processes and applications. destined to solving problems. I also have a degree in business administration, which helped me better understand the needs of the business, as well as what clients need.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Auravant | October 2021 - August 2022

Frontend development and maintenance of the company's web platform, using different languages such as Javascript (React), Jquery and Php.

Frontend Developer

Win investment | March 2021 - October 2021

Frontend development of Win investment web 3 product: company dedicated to the decentralization of the soccer market. The frontend stack used in this project were Next Js, Material Ui and web3 is.

Frontend Developer

Sagaz - Estudio creativo Digital | January 2021 - March 2021

Frontend development of the Ecommerce company Base 570. The tools used in this project are HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT AND LARAVEL.

EDUCATION



✓ Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration

Universidad de Belgrano- 2013/2019